he's going to do so he knows best here
i'm talking about apple may be
interested in buying Twitter now this is
a rumor going around as of late for the
past couple of days here that Apple is
in late negotiations with the people
over at Twitter trying to work out a
deal for around seven hundred million
dollars to buy them Apple has about
twenty nine billion dollars in cash
reserves so they have plenty of money to
work with and try some new things out
now seven hundred million dollars
there's a lot of money compared ibly to
what they have and so a lot of people
questioning this now what their Apple
should buy Twitter's that can be good
for the Twitter users or vice versa it's
going to be good for Apple is it is
smart move now I think that Twitter
right now is that a growing stage where
it has been around for a while now but
since the latest a lot of celebrities
like Oprah Ashton Kutcher p diddy Shack
a lot of these people have really puts
word on the forefront because a lot of
people always want to know the
celebrities doing the people jumping on
the bandwagon right away to see if the
celebrities are doing and I have to say
I'm subscribe to almost all done on
Oprah but and I definitely find a lot of
good information but because of those
people in the coat because the things
that they're doing actually boosted
toward her up seeing in and doing it
everybody's doing it now but Twitter
right now is not making any money from
this okay is they offering a free
service for a lot of people out there
and right now they really haven't found
out a way to actually get some ads
incorporated in here somehow that's not
intrusive to the users and start making
some money off of it kind of like
facebook facebook didn't have no ads in
the beginning but now it has millions
and millions and millions of users and
now has to find some way to support all
these people because once you get you
know millions of people you have to find
some way to maintain your service and it
does cost money to do so alpha bind them
would I don't honestly don't think it
would hurt Apple you know but I don't
think it there I don't know at what type
of direction they're going to want to
take Twitter in you know I think it
might be a good match because Apple is a
very simple company they want their
parts to be simple but sleek and sexy
and powerful and twitter is the most
simple you can get as far as updating
your friends and family just using the
180 characters I believe or less and
just let me know in about one or two
sentences what you're doing and so it
could be a good transition now I don't
think that they'll actually do it to be
honest I think the available partners
spend that seven hundred million dollars
elsewhere to make a better product or
just keep that money in the reserves for
a rainy day but would definitely see an
apple has also been rumored about
getting EA Sports my EA sports but
Electronic Arts which is EA sports but
by the domain company Electronic Arts
now they do have a good relationship
again we really don't know that I don't
think that's a good plausible move for
Apple but you never know in these days
we'll see and definitely any of these
two things are actually possible and
actually happen we'll probably more
likely hear that WWDC alright so Joe
Spencer quick update catch me on
Wednesdays a PM eastern 7 p.m. central
on ustream TV or so she knows best calm
we'll catch my livestream and subscribe
and we entered all of my giveaways here
on YouTube and I'll catch you later
peace